A Guide to the Virginia Tech Union Scrapbooks, 1969-2011
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Virginia Tech Union Scrapbooks, 1969-2011,
Special Collections, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
Virginia Tech Union
Ms2013-018
40 Cubic Feet 24 oversize boxes, 4 oversize items
A collection of scrapbooks that document the campus events organized by the Virginia Tech Union during the academic years from 1969 to 2009.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
The Virginia Tech Union Scrapbooks Collection was acquired in February 2013 from the Virginia Tech Union.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of 27 scrapbooks ranging in size from 8.5 by 11 inches to 36 by 24 inches, boxed individually. This collection also contains loose pages and documents that have been separated from their orginal scrapbook or directly relate to the Virginia Tech Union.
Administrative History
Established in 1969, the Virginia Tech Union is a student organization that provides entertainment and educational opportunities to the university community.
Index Terms
Subjects:
University History; University Archives; Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Corporate Names:
Virginia Tech Union
Contents List
- Lively Arts Season Posters, 2007-2008 (Item 1 (2 copies))
- Posters and Fliers, 2000-2011 (Box 6)
- Scrapbooks
  - 1969-1970 (Box 1)
  - 1971-1972 (Box 2)
  - 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - 1973-1974 (Box 4)
  - 1974-1975 (Box 5)
  - Separated Scrapbook Pages, 1975-1976 (Box 6)
  - 1976-1977 (Box 7)
  - 1977-1978 (Box 8)
  - 1978-1979 (Box 9, Item 2 (front and back cover))
  - Separated Scrapbook Pages, 1978-1979 (Box 6)
  - 1979-1980 (Box 10)
  - 1980-1981 (Box 11, Item 1 (front cover))
  - 1980-1983 (Box 12)
  - 1984-1986 (Box 13)
  - 1986-1987 (Box 14)
  - 1988-1989 (Box 15)
  - 1989-1990 (Box 16)
  - 1990-1991, 1998-1999 (Box 17)
  - 1992-1993 (Box 18)
  - 1993-1994 (Box 19)
  - 1994-1995 (Box 20, Item 2 (Spring cover))
  - 1995-1996 (Box 21)
  - 1996-1997 (Box 22)
  - 2005-2007 (Box 23)
  - 2007-2009 (Box 24)
  - Separated Scrapbook Pages, n.d. (Box 6)